

KHANH TRUONG

Software Engineer

Location:

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Phone:

0902.340.111

Email:

workhanh79@gmail.com

GitHub:

https://github.com/binnehaha321

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/tqk/

Website:

https://truongquockhanh.info

Summary

I am a Junior Software engineer proficient in the Front-end career path who brings a better view to the user through their experience and interaction. I have 2+ years of experience with ReactJS, using JavaScript and Typescript. I'm proficient in building brandy products (I worked on two start-up projects) and handling complex data and the logic of core features.

I am also interested in learning new things, especially to be able to serve the business's needs.

Technical Skills

Programming Languages: JavaScript, Typescript.

Frameworks: ReactJS, NextJS.

Database Management: MySQL, MS SQL Server, MongoDB.

Testing: Jest, Postman.

*I can use NodeJS to write REST API.

Tools: Figma, Sketch, Adobe XD, Slack, Trello.

Version Control System: GitHub.

Libraries: JQuery, Bootstrap, Ant Design,

TailwindCSS, MUI, ChakraUI

Others: Problem solving, Research, Teamwork.

Work Experience

Junior Developer

Feb 2023 - Present

Responsibility: Design web flows, UI/UX, and develop Helli, a young start-up product. Scoring, providing comments, and suggesting better phrases are core features. This major is complex in its working flow, with some exceptions because of integrating AI, which causes many unexpected things.

Tech stack: ReactJS, Typescript, RESTful API, Swagger.

Tools: Figma, Trello, Slack, GitHub.

Others: Ant Design, Redux Toolkit, Redux Saga.

Computing Lecturer

Sep 2022 - Present

BTEC FPT British College

Gira

Technology

Responsibility: Teaching several foundation subjects for Computer Science students There are such things as Programming (C#), Web development (HTML, CSS, PHP, MySQL), Software development Life

Cycle, and cloud computing.

Frontend Lecturer

Sep 2022 - Jun 2023

LIKELION Responsibility: Training Frontend skills: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap 5, ReactJS, RESTful API.

Fresher Developer

Nov 2021 - May 2022

Splus Software **Responsibility:** Converting design from Adobe XD, Figma, and Sketch to HTML, CSS, and JavaScript using Bootstrap for UI components Reporting and fixing bugs daily through estimated progress. Building up with the domains of E-Commerce, Branding Release, and Health Care.

Skills: HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, LESS, JavaScript, JQuery

Education

Computer Science

2019 - 2023

University of

GPA: 3.8/4.

Greenwich Classification: First honours.

Vietnam